[ movie projector whirs ]
[ water rushes down drain ]
Ohh .
WOMAN : You fixed it yet ?
Uh ... just a couple of more minutes .
[ chuckles ] You said that an hour ago .
I promised to make you dinner , right ?
Yeah . Well ...
I 'm making you a gourmet dinner .
Trust me , it 's gonna be worth the wait .
Surrender ... hmm ?
Surrender to the wonders of takeout .
Ohh .
I knew this was comin ' . [ laughs ]
' Cause when your fingers dial those seven little numbers ,
it ... it really turns me on .
Is that the best you can come up with ?
Yeah . [ doorbell buzzes ]
Wow , you are fast .
Who was it ?
I don 't know .
Well , it doesn 't even say where it 's from .
Well , there 's one way to find out .
Oh , Jamie .
You adopted us a baby .
A baby ? Honey , have you seen this thing ?
[ chuckles ] Well , who would send you a doll ?
I have no idea .
JAMIE : There 's no card , no note .
His eyes look so real .
[ comical voice ] I don 't know about you ,
but Lisa 's hungry for Chinese .
I think my wife 's gone crazy .
Oh , my God ! This reminds me of that poem from when we were kids .
What poem ?
Oh , you remember . Come on .
That old ghost story about the woman who had all those dolls .
Beware the stare of Mary Shaw .
She had no children , only dolls .
And something , something scary .
Something ... something ...
boo !
[ laughing ]
I think you 're having
just a little too much fun there , Lis .
Oh , baby , I won 't let the scary dummy hurt you .
Thank you , thank you .
[ thunder crashes ]
[ music playing on stereo ]
If you get Jamie to scream ,
I 'll make sure you get seven minutes in heaven with my old Barbie .
Deal ?
[ doll voice ] Yes , Lisa .
God , I 'm such a loser .
[ phantasmic breathing ]
[ music playing on stereo ]
Good boy .
[ distant thunder rumbles ]
â  ª ... at all â  ª
â  ª Does she make you feel warm and wanted ? â  ª
â  ª Do you know how it feels â  ª
[ music distorts ]
Jamie ?
[ music slows ]
[ music stops ]
[ clock ticking ]
[ ticking slows , stops ]
[ steam whistles ]
[ whistling stops ]
[ ambient sound dies ]
[ soft chuckling ]
[ Lisa panting softly ]
[ no audible thunder ]
Aah !
Aah ! God !
Unkh ! Ohhh !
[ gasping ]
[ retching ]
Aaaahhhhh !
[ passing horn blares ]
[ distant car alarm beeping ]
[ low , sinister rumble ]
[ steam whistling ; music plays on stereo ]
Baby , I 'm back .
[ steam whistling ]
[ grunts ] Ohh !
Lisa ! What are you trying to do , burn the place down ?
[ steam whistle dies ]
Lis !
Oh , Lisa !
LISA 'S VOICE : I 'm in here .
[ low ] Dinner in bed .
I get it .
[ slipping sound ]
Lisa !
Yes , Jamie ?
What 's going on ?
I have a surprise for you , Jamie .
[ door creaks ]
[ Lisa laughing ] Lisa , this is not funny .
[ gasps ]
[ Jamie sobs ; siren wails ]
You know what it was ?
Your mistake ?
It was the rose .
Yep . Boy , I 'll tell ya ... [ electric razor buzzes ]
... if I had a dollar for every time some guy gave his wife a rose
on the day that he ... you know .
Like that 's an alibi .
Alibi ?
[ shuts off razor ]
I didn 't hear you . Did you say something ?
Why would I need an alibi ?
I 'm sure your lawyer would want you to have one .
A lawyer ?
Yeah . I mean , the prosecution .
They 're gonna have your fingerprints ,
no signs of forced entry on your apartment ,
and you as the last person to see your wife alive ,
and that 's a lot to go up against .
You think I killed my wife .
Excuse me ?
Do you think I killed my wife ?
No . No , I don 't think you did .
I 'm just trying to help your lawyer out .
I mean , he 's gonna need something more concrete ,
I mean , at least to shift the suspicion away from you .
Suspicion ?
I-If you want to talk suspicion , why don 't you start
by looking at the package that turned up on my doorstep ?
Oh , yeah . The package , right .
Uh ... ahem ... let 's see .
You received an unmarked package
just moments before Lisa was killed .
Yeah , a package containing
a ventriloquist dummy . A ventriloquist dummy . Yeah .
Well , the mystery toy department is down the hall .
This is the homicide department ,
so unless you could tell me how some puppet
ties into your wife 's murder ,
I ... I don 't see the relevance .
In the town where I 'm from ,
a ventriloquist dummy is a bad omen .
It 's kind of a local legend ,
and some people believe
that the dummy brings death to those around them .
Okay .
Well , uh , Jamie , um ...
I 've never arrested a dummy
for murder before ...
but I have arrested quite a few husbands .
You don 't think it 's weird that this package arrives
right before Lisa is killed ?
I will tell you what I think is weird .
You said that your wife spoke to you
just moments before you found her , right ?
Yeah .
But she didn 't have a tongue .
In fact , according to you ,
she was already dead .
Now , see , to me , that 's weird .
So what are you gonna do ?
Arrest me ?
Not yet .
Look , you can go , Ashen .
You 're a free man for now .
Good .
That 'll give me more time to do your job for you .
Jamie !
Oh ...
I 'm so sorry for your loss ,
but I 'm so glad to have you home .
Ohh .
My lord , you must think I 'm so rude .
We haven 't even been introduced .
I 'm Ella .
I 'm ...
well ... [ chuckles ]
I guess I 'm your stepmother .
Is he in ? Yes , he is .
Please come in . Thanks .
There 's some things that you need to know
about your father .
I know everything I need to .
EDWARD : Ella !
Who 's down there with you ?
Your father won 't fight you , Jamie .
He doesn 't fight anyone , not anymore .
Well , then , you 're not married to my father .
EDWARD : Ella !
EDWARD : I can hear you .
My damn chair is stuck .
Here , Edward , let me help you .
My son .
What a pleasant surprise .
What happened to you ?
Your father had a stroke two months ago .
Why didn 't anybody tell me ?
You never return my calls .
It 's cause I never know what to say to you .
I take it I wasn 't the easiest person
to get along with in the past ,
but I 've changed .
Really ? Yes .
A stroke can do that to a man .
Listen ...
I 'm sorry about your wife .
I hear you 've brought her home .
Yeah . Don 't worry .
I 'll call Henry Walker , make the arrangements ...
No , that 's okay . I can take care of it .
Jamie , please .
As your father , it 's the least I can do .
You 've done the least you can do my whole life .
It 's too late for charity now .
Is that why you 've come here ,
to remind me what a bad father I 've been to you ?
In light of what has happened ,
I was hoping we could put that in the past .
I didn 't come to talk about that .
I-I came to ask you something .
Do you remember , when I was a kid ,
Mom used to read me a poem .
Do you remember what it was ?
What poem ?
Beware the stare of Mary Shaw .
She had no children , only dolls ,
and if you see her in your dreams
be sure you never , ever scream .
Then you know it ?
It just a scary poem parents would tell
their kids to keep them in line .
No , no . It 's more than just a ghost story ,
and the adults believed in it as well .
We live in a small town , Jamie .
Small minds breed small-minded superstitions , that 's all .
There 's nothing else to tell .
Nothing ?
Edward ...
your son has been through a lot .
Why don 't we make up a room for him ?
No , that 's okay . I 'm not staying long .
Got a funeral to prepare .
EDWARD : Jamie .
Jamie !
[ sighs ]
Please wait !
Won 't you stay the night here ?
It was nice meeting you , Ella .
[ sighs ] Your father 's changed .
He 's not the same man that you remember .
Really ?
Do you see that ?
Mom used to be in that picture with us ...
until he drove her to kill herself .
And his second wife ,
and that one there ...
but she was smart enough to leave .
So it 's a good thing you 're gonna outlive him , lady .
There 'll be no one to paint you out .
[ rings doorbell ] WOMAN : What more
do you want from me ?
Ohh .
Peck , peck , peck , peck , peck , peck .
I must say , I was deeply
saddened to hear the news .
If you 're up to it , I can walk you through
the various casket options we have .
Or we can do it later .
It 's okay . Let 's , uh , let 's do it now .
Now , I don 't know what your preferences are .
Have you spoken to her family yet ?
Only once .
We didn 't really talk about casket choices .
When is she arriving ?
Tonight .
Once the police have released her body ,
then I 'll pick her up .
Oh , I 'll need you to fill out
these forms at ... at your convenience .
[ neon sign buzzes rhythmically ]
[ wind whistles faintly ]
[ water drips ]
[ buzzing slows ]
[ buzzing dies ]
[ faint creaking ]
[ dripping sound slows and distorts ]
[ no audible dripping ]
[ ambient sound dies ]
FEMALE VOICE : Jamie .
SHRILL VOICE : Jamie !
[ Jamie gasps ]
[ phantasmic breathing ]
[ phantasmic groan ]
[ neon sign buzzes rhythmically ]
No , it ... it can 't be !
FEMALE VOICE : Be quiet .
FEMALE VOICE : Shh .
Shh . Marion ?
Marion , is that you ?
Marion , I told you not to go down there anymore .
Now , come out of there and go to bed .
FEMALE VOICE : She 's here now .
I know it . Marion ...
I don 't have time to play games .
She won 't find me down here .
Marion , I 'm not gonna ask you again .
Let 's go .
Come on , come on .
You just shush now .
The silent time is here .
Go on .
Go on up . I 'll be up later .
Did you see her ? Did you ?
When she killed your wife ? Did you see her do it ?
Kill my wife ? What are you talking about ?
Beware the stare of Mary Shaw .
She had no children , only dolls .
And if you see her in your dreams ...
Marion !
[ low ] She 's here . No one 's safe .
Oh , Marion .
Marion , you leave him alone .
This is not the time .
What 's she talking about ?
I 'm sorry , Jamie .
She ... she doesn 't know what she 's saying .
Come . Gonna take you home now . Let 's go .
Let 's go . Come on .
MARION : You must bury the doll .
Bury the doll !
HENRY : Leave him alone , leave him alone .
Come on , Marion , we 'll go home ...
" Billy . "
[ female voice hums " Ring Around the Rosies " ]
[ wind howls ]
[ shovel strikes earth ; Jamie pants with exertion ]
[ scrapes wooden surface ]
[ grunts with exertion ]
I dug you up .
[ wind dies completely ]
[ ambient sound dies ]
[ wind howls ]
[ phantasmic laughter ; Jamie gasps ]
[ gasping ]
[ phantasmic laughter ]
[ distant phantasmic laughter ]
[ phantasmic shriek ]
Thought I asked you not to leave the city .
I came to bury my wife . You ... you got a problem with that ?
Nope .
[ activates electric razor ]
Problem is , she 's not the only one that you came to bury .
So you 've been following me now ?
You know , Jamie ,
you really are forcing me to use
the word " perplexed " an awful lot lately .
You mind telling me ...
what the hell that is ?
Okay . Since you don 't want to answer my questions ...
maybe you 'd like to answer his .
[ clears throat ]
Why did you bury me , Jamie ?
Is it because I 'm evidence in a capital crime ,
a crime that you are the number suspect in ?
You understand what I 'm saying here ?
It 's like I told you before .
The night Lisa was murdered , somebody sent it to me .
I-It just arrived on our doorstep .
So why 'd you bury it ?
Well , it came from that cemetery .
I was just putting it back .
In the cemetery ?
There 's an old ghost story around here
about a woman named Mary Shaw .
She was buried with her doll collection .
Now , the story goes ,
if you ever see her , make sure you never scream .
Or what ?
Ohh .
Or you end up without a tongue .
I guess your wife didn 't listen , then , huh ?
You son of a ... ! Hey , hey , hey !
Settle down , Jamie .
Let 's not add assaulting an officer to your list
of offenses here .
So you 're trying to tell me
that a ghost killed your wife ?
I don 't know . I don 't know .
What do you know ?
I do know whoever sent this to me
either knows who killed my wife or did it themselves .
Hmm .
That 's a theory .
I 'm gonna go ,
and , uh , I hope you don 't mind
me taking our little friend here with me ...
seeing as he 's evidence and all .
Great .
Good night , neighbor .
Neighbor ?
Sleep tight .
You know , I noticed you have very smooth skin .
What 's your secret ?
Oh .
Well , that never works for me .
Friend of yours ?
You said Mary Shaw killed my wife .
Why would you say that ?
Marion .
Marion , please !
Shh !
There . I know .
What do you know about Mary Shaw ?
I didn 't say anything . I ...
You 're ... you 're not supposed to have that .
Where did you get that ?
Maybe you can tell me .
It hers .
Who ? Mary Shaw 's ?
We don 't say her name around here .
Oh , you don 't say her name .
Well , why don 't you try ?
Huh ?
It might just help me find out who killed my wife .
There are things you remember ...
and there are things you can 't forget .
Like the look on that woman 's face when she died .
Her name was Mary Shaw ,
the ventriloquist who lost her voice .
Back when I was a boy ,
those were the glory days of Ravens Fair ,
and the town built itself a grand old theater ,
the Guignol Theater out on Lost Lake .
[ audience applauds ]
I only ever went there once .
Where is Billy ?
Billy !
Where are you , Billy ?
BILLY : You won 't find me , Mother !
[ Billy laughs ; spectators murmur ]
I knew you were hiding out there .
You there ...
Could you check under your seat for me ?
He 's here !
Would you mind bringing him to me ?
[ scattered chuckles ]
[ applause ] Good boy !
Say thank you .
Thank you , Henry .
[ audience laughs ]
Is that right , young man ?
Is your name Henry ?
Well !
I guess my boy 's had his eye on you .
[ applause ]
Now , why did you run away , Billy ?
Don 't I treat you well ?
Oh , yes . You 're the best mother I could ever hope for .
It 's just that it gets so dusty inside that little box !
It makes me wanna ... Want to what ?
wanna ... wanna ...
Ah-choo !
[ laughter ]
Ahh !
Oh , Billy !
You sneezed all over my shoe .
[ gasps ]
[ laughter ]
I 'm sorry , Mother .
I-I can 't help it .
CHILD : I can see your lips moving !
[ audience gasps ]
What ?
Who said that ?
I did . I can see it .
Her lips are moving .
What do you say to that , Billy ?
Young Michael here doesn 't think you 're a real person .
What do you mean , Mother ?
He thinks you 're a dummy ,
and that I 'm doing your voice for you .
But that can 't be true !
There 's no way you 'd give me all the good lines !
[ audience laughs ] Forget about him , Billy !
There will always be doubters .
I don 't want to forget , Mother .
I think we should show this boy
just how real I am .
I 'm just as real as him !
No ! I 'm afraid we must go on with the show !
No ! I 'm as real as you are , and I 'll show you !
Leave him alone , Billy !
I 'll show him what it 's like , Mother !
Listen to me ! That 's enough !
I 'm as real as you ! Bring him up here ! No more !
[ audience applauds ]
Now ...
who 's the dummy ?
Some weeks later that disbelieving
little boy went missing ,
gone without a trace .
But I always felt
that Mary Shaw played some role in it ,
and not long after that ,
she was murdered .
Who killed her ?
No one ever found out .
In her will ,
Mary stated that her dummies
were to be buried with her .
Her ... her ... her children ,
as she called them ,
all 101 of them .
Her body was brought to my father 's mortuary
so he could begin work on her
other final request .
Not only did she ask to be buried with her dolls ,
she asked to become a doll herself .
[ thunder crashes ]
[ stairs creaking ]
[ loud crash ]
[ phantasmic shriek ]
Henry , are you all right ?
Ever since she was buried ,
Ravens Fair has been plagued by death .
Families murdered .
They were found without their tongues
posed in family portraits .
Your wife 's is the last .
How could you take these pictures ?
No , I have to take pictures .
It 's part of my business .
Who would have dug up the dummy and sent it to me ?
I don 't know .
No one in this town dares speak Mary Shaw 's name ,
let alone go near her grave .
They know she won 't stop killing
until the screaming does .
You said she lived out at that old theater .
Right ? The one on Lost Lake ?
Jamie ! Jamie , please !
Please be careful .
If you go looking for answers ,
you just might find them .
That 's what I 'm counting on .
Mornin ' , Mary .
Just gonna go check in on the kids .
[ strikes notes ]
[ metal clanking ]
[ wrenching sound ]
[ loud clang ]
[ wind howls ]
[ soft whirring sound ]
Momma ! Momma !
[ voice distorts ] Momma ... !
[ phantasmic laughter and applause ]
[ wind whistles ]
[ ambient sound dies ]
[ Jamie breathing ]
[ phantasmic shrieking ]
[ Jamie panting ]
MARION : What do you want with him ?
What is it ? What do you want ?
We did what you wanted .
We put you in there with your family ,
all together .
Why can 't you just leave us alone ?
FEMALE VOICE : Why won 't you ?
I didn 't ... I didn 't do anything .
Yes , you did ! You talked !
MARION : I didn 't talk ! I didn 't !
I didn 't say anything !
I ... I didn 't !
Hey !
Say something .
Why have you gone so quiet ?
I 'm putting you back where you belong .
He talked to me ! He talked to me !
Stop it ! He did ! He talked to me !
He talked to me !
[ faint creaking ]
[ indistinct female sobbing ]
[ indistinct sobbing continues ]
Marion ?
Marion , I 'm sorry I yelled at you .
[ indistinct sobbing continues ]
Marion ?
You won 't have to hide anymore .
This 'll all be over soon .
Marion ?
[ timbers creaking ]
[ sobbing continues ]
Marion , now you come on out now .
Ma ...
Marion ?
Marion , open the door .
Marion !
Come on , no games , Marion !
[ pounding door ] Open the door !
[ ambient sound dies ]
[ Henry gasping ]
Ma ... ! [ pounding door ]
Marion , open this door ! Please , Marion !
BILLY : Hello , Henry .
[ terrified sobbing ]
Oh ... oh , my God !
Aaaaahhhh !
[ phantasmic chuckling ]
[ tires squeal ]
ELLA : Jamie !
You 're just in time for dinner .
I 'm not hungry .
It 's soup .
Delicious too , if I must say so myself .
EDWARD : I 'll vouch for that .
Oh !
I didn 't come here to eat . I came to talk .
About Mary Shaw .
You lied to me .
No , I didn 't .
Sit down . No , I want the truth .
What does Michael Ashen and our family
have to do with Mary Shaw ?
Fine .
When he was a boy ,
your great-uncle , Michael Ashen ,
vanished without a trace .
Aaahhh !
EDWARD : For our family , there was only ever one suspect ...
Mary Shaw .
So they dealt their own justice .
[ indistinct angry shouting ]
They forced her to scream ...
Aaaahhhh !
... then cut out her tongue .
Our family killed her ?
Along with others from Ravens Fair .
But she didn 't stay dead .
She came back and took her revenge .
One by one ,
each of the men involved were killed ,
their tongues ripped out .
And then the same thing happened to their wives .
And then their children .
And their children 's children .
All these years you 've resented me for sending you away ,
but I did it to distance you from this curse .
Distance ?
Well , it found Lisa .
Lisa 's death made me realize
we can 't run from our fate .
Spirits have long memories .
She 'll come for us in the end .
I 'm paying for the sins of my fathers .
Jamie , I 'm sorry .
All I ever meant to do was to protect you ,
even if it earned your hatred .
I don 't know how , but one way or another ...
I 'm gonna stop this thing .
Please , son !
Well , now ! Hey there !
I was wondering if you could help me with a missing persons case .
Whoa , wait .
Wait . Looking for a male .
Brown hair . He 's around this tall .
Sometimes seen with a hand up his ass .
Actually ...
his brothers and sisters have just gone missing too .
What are you talking about ?
Somebody dug ' em up .
All one hundred of ' em .
What I want to know is ,
who did it and why ?
So do I ! Hey !
Don 't give me some ghost story about a woman who kills you if you scream ,
' cause nobody in this town 's ever heard of Mary Shaw
or your little fairy tale .
They 're lying ! They 're afraid !
Afraid of what ? Afraid of ghosts ?
Or are they afraid of talking to the cop
who 's investigating your wife 's murder ?
They have no reason to protect me .
But they believe in Mary Shaw .
That 's why they won 't answer your stupid questions .
No , it 's you who won 't answer my questions , Jamie .
That 's why I 'm gonna arrest you for stealing evidence ,
and then I 'm gonna sit you down , and you will ...
What do you want me to tell you ?
Something less perplexing than a ghost story .
Come on . Jamie .
Is everything all right ?
It 's for you .
They said it was urgent .
Go ahead .
Hello ? STATICKY VOICE : Jamie ?
Who is this ? [ static crackles ]
It 's me .
Henry ?
I can prove it .
Henry , I can 't hear you . You 're breaking up .
I ... I can prove it .
I can ... [ static crackles ] ... you didn 't kill her .
There 's a way .
A-At the theater .
Meet me at the theater . It 's on Lost Lake .
Yeah , I know where it is .
Now Jamie .
Henry , wait . W-What have you found ?
Henry ! Henry !
That was Henry Walker from the funeral home .
He says he can prove I didn 't kill my wife .
Oh . Convenient time for him to call .
Let 's go . Wait , wait , wait .
I 'm gonna meet him at the theater . That 's where I 'm going .
No , you 're going with me . Your appointment with me comes first .
You wanted answers . I 'm giving you answers .
Game 's over .
I 'm done with the ghost stories . Let 's go .
We 're talking about my wife here . Come on .
Do us both a favor , Jamie .
Don 't make me cuff you in front of your mom .
Jamie !
Jamie ! Jamie !
Hey ! You don 't want to make me chase you ! Jamie !
I don 't have a full tank of gas !
DETECTIVE : Jamie !
Henry !
Jamie !
Hello !
Where are you ?
Henry !
Henry .
HENRY 'S VOICE : Come on , Jamie . I 'm up here .
HENRY 'S VOICE : I 'm in here .
Henry .
Guess again .
He 's here .
Nobody 's here .
Our boots were the only two out there .
I 'm telling you , he 's here .
And I 'm telling you ,
he is not here !
HENRY 'S VOICE : Yes , he is .
You say , " I told you so , "
I 'll shoot you .
Where the hell are you ?
[ female voice hums " Ring Around the Rosies " ]
Hey .
Hang onto this for a second .
Jamie , where you going ?
Remember , whatever happens ,
don 't scream .
Jamie .
Jamie ?
Jamie !
[ low ] What ?
You follow me .
[ low ] Yes , sir .
[ scurrying sounds ]
All right , Jamie .
Where is he ?
You know , if I see one more of these ...
They 're all here .
Yep .
All home .
[ pigeons cooing ]
Someone brought them back here .
All but one .
What ?
What the hell is that ?
Is that a doll ?
It 's not a doll .
It 's a boy .
You mean it was a boy .
[ terrified gasp ]
[ pigeons cooing ]
It 's me .
All right , I get it .
I think we just solved a 70-year-old missing persons case .
And who was that ?
A long-lost relative .
[ ambient sound dies ]
This is how it starts .
What 's going on here , Jamie ?
[ faint creaking sound ]
[ creaking sound ]
Jamie .
[ faint metallic squeak ]
[ creaking sound ]
[ faint creaking sound ]
[ creaking sounds ]
What the ... ?
[ rhythmic creaking sound ]
[ rhythmic creaking continues ]
Mary Shaw ?
[ rhythmic creaking stops ]
[ louder ] Mary Shaw .
RASPY VOICE : Clever .
DETECTIVE : Who 's there ?
Show yourself !
Come on !
What do you want ?
To silence all those
who silenced me .
Is that why you killed Michael Ashen ?
So hard to construct
the perfect doll .
Sometimes you have to use
existing parts .
I love you , Mommy . I love you , Mommy .
MICHAEL 'S VOICE : I love you , Mommy .
I love you , Mommy ... [ voice trails off ]
Why Lisa ?
Why 'd you take her from me ?
Come closer
and I 'll tell you .
D-Don 't go back there .
Don 't . Come on , come on , don 't go .
RASPY VOICE : Come closer !
I 'll whisper it to you !
You weren 't the last Ashen .
The last Ashen was inside her .
LISA 'S VOICE : Oh , Jamie !
You adopted us a baby .
Ohh !
[ sinister laughter ]
Don 't scream .
[ cocks shotgun ]
[ phantasmic shriek ]
[ glass shatters ]
What the hell 's going on here , Jamie ?
What 's going on ?
She 's living in the dolls .
What ? ! She 's living in the dolls !
[ phantasmic shriek ]
Destroy the dolls ! I am !
All the dolls !
[ childlike screams ]
DETECTIVE : Jamie !
Come on !
DETECTIVE : Come on !
Aaaaaahhhhhh !
Aaaaahhhhhhh !
[ metal groans ]
[ electric razor buzzes ]
[ panting ]
[ metal groaning ]
[ stifles scream ]
[ gasping ]
[ panting ]
One left .
Henry !
[ distant thunder rumbles ]
[ indistinct sobbing ]
MARION : [ sobbing ] Please ! Please !
[ sobbing continues ]
Plea ... Please !
Please ... say ...
something !
Shit !
Marion ! Marion , listen to me , where is the dummy ?
H-He took it .
Who took it ? Who took it ? !
Mr. A-Ashen .
Mr. Ash ...
Marion , my father is in a wheelchair .
He never leaves the house .
He left this house .
He h-had the doll .
It was him .
[ sobbing ]
[ thunder rumbles ]
[ clock ticking ]
[ ambient sounds die ]
[ door creaks faintly ; Jamie breathing ]
[ footfalls ]
[ door creaks ]
[ Jamie breathing ]
DETECTIVE 'S VOICE : Why did you bury me , Jamie ?
HENRY 'S VOICE : I 'm in here !
[ chimes tinkling ]
[ phantasmic shriek ]
Aaaaaahhhhhh !
[ thunder crashes ]
[ rain falls steadily ]
[ footfalls ]
Dad ?
I take it I wasn 't the easiest person
to get along with in the past , but I 've changed .
Jamie !
ELLA 'S VOICE : Soup ! Delicious too .
EDWARD 'S VOICE : I 'll vouch for that .
HENRY 'S VOICE : Jamie , I can prove you didn 't kill her .
[ phantasmic shriek ]
ELLA 'S VOICE : Jamie !
I 'm so glad to have you home !
[ low , sobbing moan ]
MARY SHAW 'S VOICE : Now who 's the dummy ?
[ phantasmic laughter ] No !
Aaaaaahhhhh ! [ sickening thud ]
MARY SHAW 'S VOICE : Shhhh !
JAMIE 'S VOICE : Beware the stare of Mary Shaw .
She had no children , only dolls .
And if you see her in your dreams ,
be sure you never , ever scream .
[ " Who 's Holding You Now ? " begins playing ]
JOHNETTE NAPOLITANO : â  ª Are you in the arms of a stranger â  ª
â  ª It 's dangerous â  ª
â  ª The way I 'm feeling â  ª
â  ª So disconnected â  ª
â  ª So rejected â  ª
â  ª Staring at the ceiling â  ª
â  ª From the side of the bed â  ª
â  ª Remembering things that you said â  ª
â  ª And now you 're saying to someone else â  ª
â  ª I am ready to scream â  ª
â  ª This is all a bad dream â  ª
â  ª And I am beside myself â  ª
â  ª Who 's holding you now ? â  ª
â  ª Who 's holding you ? â  ª